<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Younes Belkada's blog</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Younes Belkada's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</managingEditor><webMaster>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Imitation Learning explained</title><link>http://example.org/posts/imitation_learning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/imitation_learning/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/posts/robot-reading.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Here is my attempt to explain the notions and intuitions behind Imitation Learning with the best of my knowledge. Credits to this very nice blog where I have learned most of the things that I have understood about the concept, and to this website for the image above. Now let&rsquo;s directly dive in.
1. Brief intuitions In Reinforcement Learning, you learn to make good sequence of decisionsSource: http://web.stanford.edu/class/cs234/slides/lecture1.pdf
" In Reinforcement Learning, you learn to make good sequence of decisions  The field of Reinforcement Learning is an area of machine learning where an intelligent agent interacts with an environment in order to learn a policy (i.]]></description></item><item><title>Challenge 1 - Brain Tumor classification on Kaggle</title><link>http://example.org/posts/brain_tumor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/brain_tumor/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/projects/brain.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>We decided with my friend Arthur Zucker to challenge ourselves into this Kaggle competition. The project looks quite exciting, with a serious and challenging application on a real-wolrd problem. According to the official Kaggle repository: A malignant tumor in the brain is a life-threatening condition. Known as glioblastoma, it&rsquo;s both the most common form of brain cancer in adults and the one with the worst prognosis, with median survival being less than a year.]]></description></item></channel></rss>