<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Projects - Category - Younes Belkada's blog</title><link>http://example.org/categories/projects/</link><description>Projects - Category - Younes Belkada's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</managingEditor><webMaster>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/projects/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>InterfaceGAN++: How far can we go with InterfaceGAN?</title><link>http://example.org/posts/interface-gan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/interface-gan/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/images/posts/interfacegan.gif" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>I would like to explain in this post, one the projects I was involved during my Masters degree at ENS Paris Saclay, during the Introduction to Numerical Imaging course.
Introduction InterfaceGAN is a paper that has been published on CVPR 2020, by Yujin Shen et al. It argues that well-trained generative models learns a disentangled latent space representation.
Basically given a generated face image from a random gaussian noise, InterfaceGAN can control some specific attributes of the face without altering the semantic information of it.</description></item><item><title>A frist approach for steganography using Language Models</title><link>http://example.org/projects/stego-ml/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/projects/stego-ml/</guid><description>Introduction This project was conducted upon the EPFL CS-433 course, for a semester project, during the fall semester 2020. This project tries to find a novel approach for steganography applied to text data using Language Models.
What is Steganography ? The principle of Steganography is to hide a secret message inside another message or in an image. These techniques can be used to avoid Man In the Middle (MITM) attacks and send secret messages to a pre-defined receiver.</description></item><item><title>In-the-wild eye contact detection for Autonomous Vehicles</title><link>http://example.org/projects/looking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/projects/looking/</guid><description>The method performs in-the-wild eye contact detection" The method performs in-the-wild eye contact detection Problem statement The task of in-the-wild eye contact detection for autonomous agents is under-estimated in the Deep Learning literature today. To the best of our knowledge, there are very few studies about this task and there is a lack of labeled dataset for the latest. Eye-contact detection in the context of autonomous driving is extremely challenging and useful.</description></item><item><title>An approach for fitness exercise scoring using Deep Learning</title><link>http://example.org/projects/pose-socring/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 20:26:19 +0200</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/projects/pose-socring/</guid><description>Introduction Imagine a world where (almost) everything is powered by Artificial Intelligence. Today, some signs of an Artifical Intelligence-guided society are coming into existence. Autonomous cars can automately drive you from a point A to a point B, and more recently, Tesla has revealed the Tesla Bot, the humanoid robot that will be able to help humans for simple tasks.
Elon Musk when revealing the Tesla Bot - August 2021 -Source: autoplus.</description></item><item><title>An unsupervised method for table structure recognition</title><link>http://example.org/projects/table-structure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 20:26:19 +0200</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/projects/table-structure/</guid><description>Problem statement Some organizations still use huge amounts of scanned tables / invoices. Rather than manually typing the contents of the tables into an excel file, one can think of using Deep Learning to tackle this problem. Once you identify the distinguishable cells on the tables, we can pass an OCR (Optical Character Recognition) to each cell to read its contents and convert it to an excel file for example.</description></item><item><title>Mathematic Modelling of Natural Selection phenomena</title><link>http://example.org/projects/modelisation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 20:26:19 +0200</pubDate><author>younesbelkada@gmail.com (Younes Belkada)</author><guid>http://example.org/projects/modelisation/</guid><description>Problem statement During my first academic project, we focused on how we can represent quantitative and qualitative evoluation of a population in a context of competition, reproduction and mutation. This project was conducted together with the LCQB lab at Sorbonne University.
The natural selection phenomena is hard to modelise due to various factors" The natural selection phenomena is hard to modelise due to various factors The report of the work (in French) can be found here as well as the poster of the presentation here</description></item></channel></rss>